A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Administration, Program and Policy, RG 3 FA112
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administration, Program and Policy, 2
  - Environmental Affairs, 927
    - Environmental Affairs - Fellowships, 1973-1984; 927.E; 26 document cases
      - Maidment, David R., 1975-1980 (Box 14, Folder 87)
      - Maidment, David R., 1975-1980 (Box 14, Folder 88)
      - Maidment, David R. - Supplementary Material, 1977, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 89)
      - Martin, Brian, 1976-1981 (Box 15, Folder 90)
      - Melosi, Martin V., 1975-1977, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 91)
      - M'Gonigle, Robert M., 1976-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 92)
      - Miller, Sterling, 1974-1977, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 93)
      - Miller, Sterling - Supplementary Material, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 94)
      - Miller, Sterling - Supplementary Material, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 95)
      - Myhra, David, 1977-1981 (Box 16, Folder 96)
      - Myhra, David - Supplementary Material, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 97)
      - Nalven, Joseph, 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 98)
      - Nature Conservancy - R. Michael Wright, 1974-1978, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 99)
      - Nature Conservancy - R. Michael Wright - Supplementary Material, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 100)
      - Nigh, Ronald B., 1975-1976, 1978, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 101)
      - Ozkaynak, A. Haluk, 1974-1976, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 102)
      - Page, R. Talbot, 1977-1978, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 103)
      - Partridge, Ernest, 1978-1981, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 104)
      - Partridge, Ernest, 1978-1981, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 105)
      - Partridge, Ernest - Supplementary Material (Box 18, Folder 106)
      - Peskin, Sarah, 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 107)
      - Peskin, Sarah - Supplementary Material, 1976, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 108)
      - Powell, David E., 1977-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 109)
      - Quinlan, Alician V., 1975-1981 (Box 19, Folder 110)
      - Quinlan, Alician V., 1975-1981 (Box 19, Folder 111)
      - Quinlan, Alician V., 1975-1981 (Box 19, Folder 112)
      - Quinlan, Alician V. - Supplementary Material (Box 19, Folder 113)
      - Reiniger, Clair, 1976-1978, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 114)
      - Reiniger, Clair - Supplementary Material, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 115)
      - Risebrough, Robert W., 1978-1980 (Box 20, Folder 116)
      - Rose, Richard C., 1977-1980, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 117)
      - Rosenfield, Patricia L., 1975-1978, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 118)
      - Rosenfield, Patricia L., 1975-1978, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 119)
      - Rosenfield, Patricia L. - Supplementary Material, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 120)
      - Rosenfield, Patricia L. - Supplementary Material, 1976-1978, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 121)
      - Rosenfield, Patricia L. - Supplementary Material, 1976-1978, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 122)
      - Rosenfield, Patricia L. - Supplementary Material, 1976-1978, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 123)
      - Rosenfield, Patricia L. - Supplementary Material, 1976-1978, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 124)
      - Roskoski, Joann, 1976-1981 (Box 21, Folder 125)
      - Roskoski, Joann - Supplementary Material, 1976-1977, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 126)
      - Roskoski, Joann - Supplementary Material, 1976-1977, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 127)
      - Sanger, James S., 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 128)
      - Sanger, James S. - Supplementary Material, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 129)
      - Sanger, James S. - Supplementary Material, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 130)
      - Sahr, Robert C., 1975 (Box 22, Folder 131)
      - Short, James L., 1977-1979 (Box 22, Folder 132)
      - Short, James L. - Supplementary Material (Box 22, Folder 133)
      - Shuval, Hillel I., 1977-1979, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 134)
      - Sjoblad, Roy D., 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 135)
      - Spear, Robert C., 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 136)
      - Sterne, Rickie E., 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 137)
      - Sterne, Rickie E. - Supplementary Material, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 138)
      - Stockdale, Jerry D., 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 139)
      - Straffin, Philip D., 1977-1979 (Box 23, Folder 140)
      - Straffin, Philip D. - Supplementary Material, 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 141)
      - Sullivan, Arthur L., 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 142)
      - Taub, David Milton, 1975-1977, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 143)
      - Teitelbaum, Joel, 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 144)
      - Teitelbaum, Joel, 1975-1978, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 145)
      - Tilton, Donald L., 1975-1977 (Box 24, Folder 146)
      - Tilton, Donald L. - Supplementary Material, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 147)
      - Tilton, Donald L. - Supplementary Material, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 148)
      - Tully, Frank P., 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 149)
      - Vanderpol, Alvin H., 1975-1977 (Box 25, Folder 150)
      - Wallace, Anne D., 1978-1980 (Box 25, Folder 151)
      - Watson, Donald, 1977-1980 (Box 25, Folder 152)
      - Whittemore, Alice, 1975-1980 (Box 25, Folder 153)
      - Whittemore, Alice, 1975-1980 (Box 25, Folder 154)
      - Whittemore, Alice - Supplementary Material, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 155)
      - Witter, Henry L., 1976-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 156)
      - Zucchetto, James J., 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 157)
      - Zucchetto, James J. - Supplementary Material, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 158)
  - Geographic Medicine, 928
    - Geographic Medicine - Fellowships, 1977-1987; 928.E; 3 document cases
      Individual files for career development fellowships in geographic medicine.
      - Befus, A. Dean, 1979-1985, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Befus, A. Dean, 1979-1985, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Befus, A. Dean - Supplementary Material, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Befus, A. Dean - Supplementary Material, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Befus, A. Dean - Supplementary Material, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Befus, A. Dean - Supplementary Material - Reprints, 1980-1986 (Box 2, Folder 0005a)
      - Befus, A. Dean - Supplementary Material, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 0005b)
      - Jayawardena, Anil, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Jayawardena, Anil - Supplementary Material, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Jayawardena, Anil - Supplementary Material, N. D. (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Nogueira, Nadia, 1978-1985, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Nogueira, Nadia, 1978-1985, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Nogueira, Nadia - Supplementary Material, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Nogueira, Nadia - Supplementary Material, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Sher, Alan, 1978-1981, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Sher, Alan, 1978-1981, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)